Voices collide, the storm and the flame Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
Torchlight and hair
psyche's show
Who says J-Doc's not here?
Umm...
I'm in my cool little neon room today.
Check my new gaming setup.
Then it just goes down.
I have it set up a little bit better than it was though.
But I can make any kind of poster I want.
how are we doing today guys I don't know I went to beat us and like watched a
little bit you know it's fine actually thing she's being nice and it's like
expected it's like you know of course it's gonna be like oh it's just a big
misunderstanding right or like I hope it really was you know or maybe she was
joking or something like but I mean and then it's like you know
RGs over there making like those jokes, but they're not really, it's not funny to joke
about these things, especially in the day and age when these things are happening, and
like, especially in this community when some of these things are actually happening too.
And so, you know, just to be like, you don't want to like, you know, claim involvement
or act as an explorer, and be accepting of these, at least like, these, you know, these
Yeah, I saw I saw yeah, they're saying oh, and you're just friends with me because yeah
You're trying to do this and that like or you're you know trying to annoy her and I'm trying to annoy her and
Like I don't I don't know it's like
You know you just been you know supportive
for the very for the most part, you know and
It's like she has mods that I don't like or that don't like me
You know it's like I just don't like because they don't like me. I mean there's like a lot of people
Hey, what's up Rudy? There's a lot of really negative people in there
They're all talking about the cat or Tom the elbow on the panel saying oh well
Let's go take his cats like because you all read him a litter box
He didn't or you know and he didn't take it like whatever. I mean come on
It's like whatever she had my address that she wants to send me a little box
She sent me a little box, but I don't make her to send me when I have some you know, it's like hi Rudy. Hi
How are you? Oh?
Yeah, and then the cats have fleas. Yeah, because it's like they you know
They pick up fleas like sometimes like in certain times of the season and stuff like that
They are outdoor cats. I comb them off as good as I can and I will get some flea medicine
I just put three minutes a lot of them like last month. It kind of wears off, you know
Hi, baby
Hi
Actually, it means it's not like but it's like I do comb them a lot like you know, that's like a way to
To deal with like a lot of them, you know, hi
Fortunately, there's feets around here.
But they're not all wonderin' if we give you cats SCDs.
They're all fixed except for tricks.
Yeah, I see what they're sayin' about us,
and it's not very nice, but some people in the chat
are just worse than people that are on the panel.
Vita's not really going after me.
She's like, no, she's kinda putting me down a little bit,
but she's like.
You know, she's not being as bad as she was the other day. I think she's calmed down a little bit, which is good
But you know the chat is like like a lot of bullies in here are people that the kid you throw another zone
Yeah, she's good. This is this is mr. Root Rudy. He's like a little older cat
He's like 16 or 17 years old the family friend gave him to me this year
They take care of him his old age. Oh
Like that. Oh, yeah
I know, it's like they're just being like, you know,
doing some dumb.
I mean, Rupita's like being rational, you know,
and she's like trying to, you know,
it's like kind of sounds more like rational, but, you know.
Yeah, he's an old, he's an old man, Rudy.
He's the old man at house, but you know,
all the cats like him.
This sweetheart cat.
And yeah, you go outside now and you like to you still go outside and like I used to go outside and
Explore a little bit, you know, he's like
Thought he'd be like more of a house cat, but he likes it
But did you see like yeah, but Lola is getting the the mice like Lola brought in a mouse left it on the table last night
Oh, it was like just right in front of me on the table
And she's like yeah, she's like so proud of herself and like so it's so like it's really was like a gift
She's trying to give me the gift of this mouse
I was like, thank you, and you have to like be nice. Hey, Jamie. How are you?
Yeah, we're so soft so you're very soft cat. Yes, very soft cat and
You just be hard. It's like just hearing your problems and your ribs. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Curling up. Okay.
Let's curl up.
Here we go.
Through your...
The odds are there but yeah, I think it was like kind of like not really defending me too much like but that's understandable there
But they're like oh my god. He like
He didn't like every cat and I do take care of my cats and it's like and then it's like
It's really disturbing, you know because it's like it's like the same thing as like people having kids and people like saying
Oh, that's a bad mom but sometimes they are really bad, especially if they're absentee fathers or like
You know like or like moms that are like on on meth and stuff with the kid
I mean that's like kind of like there could be like a bad mom's bad dad's love like that, but
When they which we're talking about people that are just like, you know, like these are these are like, you know
They're actually good parents
Judging them for what a quote whatever thing saying that the bad parents because of this or that
I think that that's gets you personal all right
It's like not there because it's not really but any of these business unless it's like there's like some kind of abuse or something like that
And that's like nor neglect and I don't there's this is me any of that of course not like
and I've been showing my cats every day on the camera like every you know
streamed every day until the cats are well taken care of and happy and and
they're never in distress or
You know, none of them are the hungry or anything. They're all good, so
There's no reason to threaten to do that, but people are they're they're friendly and it's like she's not putting a stop to a thing
Hey, you know, but like that's a thicket super. So don't give people like you don't don't say that before like
They're all sort of being a mass and like, I mean
I'm already getting like harass and getting stuff sent to my house and stuff. So I really like
Um, you know, I don't have that, I do, it's a rooty.
So anyway, what's up, Gaudi, how are you?
I'm good, Gaudi, how are you?
Good to see ya.
Yeah, I do have a couple of new songs from here, and it's like a new thing I do, it's
the astrological sign, or the astrological placement.
Like I've done, you know, you've heard,
I had the little Scorpio song,
and you know,
capricorn rising, Aquarius moon.
Yeah, that's all.
Okay, yeah, there's that song too.
But I did, so I'm doing like more placement.
And so I have like, you know,
but I think it's a good way, you know,
you can like try to do it too, to make songs,
or it's like you can have me do it if you want me to.
And, and I'll do it, but,
Yeah, I can go through your placements and like just give you songs about like your most important placements
These are like ways to connect with your chart. I would say and also
To like, you know, there's so many bad things we put in our subconscious and we put like good things in our subconscious
like especially if they're about us and like
Or just seems to contemplate of things we want to remember
It's a good way to remember things to put them in songs and so it's like especially if you can like make these songs now
I can help you, I can even train you how to do it, like I do it, but yeah, you can, like, hire me for consulting, I think I have one by, um, takingweekends.com, and you have, like, a place you can sign up for, like, an hour of consulting, or, like, a reading, um, an hour of reading, or I think it's half hours, or something, I don't know how I had to have it set up, but I'm pretty reasonable.
Great, but it will serve you for a long time.
You're good, good to see you.
Okay, so I'll show you an example.
So this is my Aquarius, so this is my Aquarius Moon.
It's called Aquarius Moon Man, okay.
And I have a slideshow.
I'm gonna make into a good video,
but I still have to make,
I just have the pictures for it right now.
So what do I have?
Ready, let me see.
That's a serious, okay.
So I need to go get.
And I know some people aren't into this, but I'm not just generating them, I'm putting
a lot of input into it, and that's the thing, the prompt you put in has a lot to do with
the result.
That's why I get really good results, and also I do multiple things, and I do put a
lot of my input into it, including writing out most of the songs.
Also, I wouldn't be able to produce data at the aid of this intelligence because I do not know how to play a thousand instruments or have a professional recording studio and all these people that cost literally like $20,000.
Okay, so let me see. This is my query, so I think this is a little bit of a mistake.
But also, nowadays, the intelligence is getting so good that it actually gets to know you and, like,
and so, I think that makes a big difference in the amount of it, too.
Like, how your interaction with them. Okay, I think this is a little...
Okay, enjoy the song.
See if it's any good.
Tell me a scale one to ten after you hear it, I'm going to put up the image route you like it
He drifts where the echoes never
Pretty good, huh? That was pretty good. Hey, be a clumsy. Yeah, and this is like, I know this is a different clumsy than the one
That's in the other chat because the other guy is like, it's a jerk.
I hate that guy, but I like this one.
Yeah, um, this is a friendlier chat today, I think.
I don't know, at least all of her trolls, all of my trolls seem to be in there.
That's cool. Yeah, but um
But yeah, if you'd like me to make doing your astrological placements into a song, and then I'll be a company slideshow, and I'll put it into a video, and stuff like that, if you'd like that.
I mean, it would be a really nice thing to have, I think, but, you know, or I could show you how to do it too.
Okay
Yeah
It's a parody. Yeah, I know Sam and Sam and heads him kind of like
He's like what's this? He's talking about some kind of war or something. I don't know
Do you like that Jamie take that song a
Query yes, I'm
Pretty good. The only thing is like it's like I think they cut off at like four minutes and so so sometimes I guess they
I don't know why they designed the song longer than they could keep it, but it didn't like that, so I might
Or I have to figure out where I can cut it off
Take my there thing. Hey, how are you? Yeah, you like that? Yeah
I'm playing with some cool cool things like graphics like
Video file like this is pretty cool like you can animate pictures
kind of looks like me, I thought I had like a lot better looking.
Uh, what else?
This is the ultimate NC I know, and it's like, I think she, hopefully she recognizes that, like,
I want to show you something.
This is your shit. You don't leak your shit, but I'm all
Like fucking here's thing bro. What did you do your hair? Hold on? What are you talking about?
Are you bald? What's going on? Did you have hair? Yeah, I'm a skinhead. I'm a fucking. I'm a fucking peckerwood, dude
What are you talking about fucking I eat all day? San Bernardino peckerwoods. Okay, I
Dated a peckerwood when I was in LA County Jail. I know you told me about it. I know hey, here's the guy
Hey, man, listen, I'm being serious right now, dog.
Like fucking, I have to move out of here
where I live right now.
Fucking, hey, I might come through.
Can I chill?
Yeah.
Where are you, where are you in like Santa Monica?
Or was it?
We're on a beach, we're on a beach.
We don't like fucking, here's the thing, bro.
Fucking, yeah, I'll come through, dude.
Type shit, you know what I mean?
Like fucking, yeah, you're cool, dude.
Like, you know, fuck, hey, here's the thing,
No, I'm not gonna say that I'm not on the internet, you know, I mean, okay, okay, we'll talk privately. Okay. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but like your thing like
Yeah, it's like I'll hit you up like you have an Instagram or something like fucking don't leak your shit
Don't leak your shit, but I'm all
I'll fucking I'll come through you listen. I'll have money. I'll have hella money
I have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I when I have to leave this house
I have a hundred thousand dollars in my bank come on type shit, but you know me, so
Yeah, we'll fucking hey, we'll listen a money talks broke you guys want to see me and psych fucking on chatter bait
How much
How much? You know what I mean? Like, I'm down. I'm, you know what I mean?
Type shit.
So, anyway.
Nice. Okay, here, here's the kitty cat.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, I was, I was like, you know what I mean? I was like, have my hat. I was on my hat.
I'm like, hey, hey, it's like, hey bro, hey bro, you know what I mean?
Oops
What the fuck oh my gosh
That love it. I always like I love I love the crazy guys
No, that's terrible terrible bad. He's bad
I do want him to shout out to Time, and he was in Beed's Chat, and I thought he was speaking up for me.
That was one person. I mean, I think maybe there's a few others that don't really mind me.
There's a lot of people that were mean, like, nags was mean.
And then, you know, like, RG and, like, before Elda was being sold, and Sam was being fine.
That weird
She's making out with an alien
But they call it query is
Query is moving they call it like that cool. You can make it any kind of poster have opposed
I have any poster in the background
Wow, that's amazing. Have any poster in the world
Well, I can't show you like you know naked
It's pretty cool though, I love that, I think, peaceful.
Reminds me of, yeah, an alien.
Yeah, so, let me go back, I'm making some clips right now.
I don't know if they're posted yet, but let me,
we're back.
You hear me too? Yeah, I'm so I'm able in stream yard. It's pretty cool
I'm able to like they make they will make you some clips out of like your shows
But only the past 50 hours, but there's a lot of these shows that were actually like I
Had to delete because of like certain things
and so
But then it's like I'm not even but not all of them are available to publish. I don't know why I think
to figure that out but I think I can save them and learn myself but I'm
hosting a bunch of them right now it takes a while for these ones to finish
they take a long time but they post really fast and then not all of them
work for work for it but let me see this one is good nope not available
I'm ready to generate, okay.
That one.
I can do multiple ones at a time.
All right, do you hear me, too?
Okay, so no one's here, so, oh, two people in the chat.
Okay, well, so I guess I'll play my other AI song,
and then, or something, I shouldn't call it yet,
we'll call it my astrology song.
Let's see.
I'm sorry, I was a bit distracted.
This is called Hidden Arrows.
Okay, this is my Venus in Sagittarius song.
Let me just make some room for the art.
I think you will, oops, not that one.
I'll enjoy this.
Okay.
And thank you for coming today. I'm just gonna play this. I'm gonna try to get some more shorts up today
But this is really cool. So this is my Venus and
sedentary is slide show
Yeah, yep, yep, okay
And anymore
Okay, and I'll okay enjoy this song and then I'll uh, I'll see you later
where secrets are kept. Venus hides softly, where dreams intercept. In the 12th house of fire,
shadows ignite. Sagittarius aims through the dark toward the light. You love like a pilgrim,
on paths never known. Seeking the sacred, where wild stars are sown.
Your heart is a compass, it points past the veil
Total love that is boundless, a myth on the trail
Hello, can you hear me now, yes, can you hear me. Better?
I don't know. So, yeah, so that was weird on me. Let me try to refresh this.
Okay, see it works, okay.
Okay, crash, and then I fix it, okay.
And what else?
Okay, I have to do the bathroom real quick,
so I'm gonna put on the music,
or I'll put on the video real quick.
This is a good video.
in shadows, fears, and strong.
I hope you guys are over here.
Hello guys, I'm trying to stream on Kik too.
I mean, you can go ahead and follow me there,
Psyche Awakens.
Follow me Facebook, Psyche Awakens.
You can follow me TikTok, Psyche Awakens, Tarot.
Follow me Pinterest, Psyche Awakens.
I'm usually Psyche Awakens.
I'm not Psyche Awakens, Tarot, occasionally.
You can go to PsycheAwakens.com.
Also, I will have...
I love you guys, thanks for being here, I'll be back today, muah!
from the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls
this is psyche awakens crowd whoosh sparkly chimes
thunder crack
you smooth mystical
yo welcome to the madness buckle in tight
tear it on deck third eye in flight
truce get told he goes unfold
we stir the soul with a t-surf cold
panels be poppin' trolls be droppin'
Spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Sly for your wake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's soul deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Sly for your wake, can't ston't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream